propertymanthan.com 2016-03-14

# Property Manthan - Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

**(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views.  
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.  
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us.  
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.  
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us. 

**(2) Cookies**

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies. 

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. 

**(3) Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. 

We may use your personal information to:  
(a) administer the website  
(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website  
(c) enable your use of the services available on the website  
(d) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications  
(e) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested  
(f) provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user  
(g) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website 

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing. 

**(4) Other disclosures**

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:  
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law  
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings  
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)  
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling. 

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. 

**(5) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be temporarily stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. However, we are committed to store your data in a secured environment. 

**(6) Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology. 

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. 

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will NEVER ask you for your password other than when you log in to the website. 

**(7) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email. 

**(8) Your rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to a fee. 

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by using your account communications preferences at any time. 

**(9) Communication**

If the Builder, Agent/Broker or any individual has provided their contact information for everyone to see then users can contact them at their request. 

**(10) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. 

**(11) Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. 

**(12) Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us using the feedback form.
